Guide to the Ed Wood, Jr. collection, 1966-2006.
Wood, Ed Jr. collection
- Series I. Novels
  - The Perverts By: Edward D. Wood, Jr. Pseudonym: Jason Nichols, 1968; Pages: 160 (Box 2)
    [a proposed socio-cultural study of contemporary perversions and ‘deviations’, topics include Necrophilia, Troilism, Prostitution, Fetishes, S&M, Bestiality, Homosexuality, Transvestitism, Incest, Lesbianism. Page 52: Man will seek out woman wherever he is – the steaming jungles of the Amazon or the same steaming jungles of his own home town. SEX WILL OUT! And there will always be the whore to take care of his needs. She might be hidden or she might be out in the open. The law will close up her PUSSY for a time, but once she is released the PUSSY will again be open for business. In thinking along the same thoughts the women of the world are also looking for their own whore – THE MALE WHORE! There is a fellow who will sell his body to women for a price. The thoughts even there must go back along the lines of history to the oiled-down frames of the males who were sent to the ruler’s chambers for the night."] excerpt trans section
  - The Sexecutives By: Edward D. Wood, Jr. Pseudonym: David L. Westermier, 1968; Pages: 160 (Box 2)
    Cover art may be by Paul Rader, recycled from a lesbian pulp novel. [PROOF?]
    [Surrounds a group of sex spies, "Instant Secretaries, Inc." Was later turned into the Foto-Reader For Love Or Money.] excerpt heavily
  - The Svengali of Sex By: Edward D. Wood, Jr. Pseudonym: Edgar Andrews, 1968; Pages: 157 (Box 2)
    [Svengali concerns the exploits of a hypno-therapist, Larry, who gives his hypnotized female patients the full-treatment. Page 111: "Under hypnosis at least, she no longer thought of that. Shirley stood in front of the mirror, turning this way and that to look at herself. The look on her face was one of critical satisfaction. Now she turned to face Larry. "I think you’re right." Larry got up and joined her at the mirror. Casually he placed his hand around her waist. ‘Now Shirley,’ he said, ‘can’t you see for yourself that any normal man would certainly like you – almost instantly would want to make love to you?’ Shirley looked up at him but her eyes were on his lips. Softly she said, ‘Would you?’" Page 137: "Larry kissed and sucked her breasts and used his hands on her love triangle and her hot, moist crevice so that in a very few minutes she was moaning and crying in her ecstasy." Photos from a B & B Productions motion picture.]
  - Young, Black and Gay By: Edward D. Wood, Jr., 1968; Pages: 158 (Box 2)
    Publisher: Publishers Export Co., Inc./French Line Novel, San Diego
    A PEC French Line novel
    [Rudolph Grey writes: "A homosexual transvestite adapts to prison life, taking the female sex role while absorbing convict philosophy. He winds up the victim of a brutal beating in a filthy alley."]
  - A Study of the Lesbian the Homosexual the Bi-sexual By: Edward D. Wood, Jr. Pseudonym: Dr. T. K. Peters with S. T. Lee, no year/c. 1969/70; Pages: 192 (Box 2)
    Publisher: SECS Press, Los Angeles
    Photo Illustrated (color/b&w)
    "Sex Education Clinical Series vol. XI"
    [double check to see if this is Wood]
  - Let Me Die in Drag By: Edward D. Wood, Jr. Pseudonym: Woodrow Edwards, 1969; Pages: 192 (Box 2)
    Publisher: Classic Publications, Los Angeles
    [reissue of Death of a Transvestite]
  - Male Wives By: Edward D. Wood, Jr. Pseudonym: Norman Bates, 1969; Pages: 191 (Box 2)
    Publisher: Barclay House, North Hollywood
    A Barclay House Psycho-Sex Study
    [Bibliography includes Hollywood Babylon by Kenneth Anger, The Seven Pillars of Wisdom by T. E. Lawrence, and more, as well as many adult books.]
  - The Oralists By: Edward D. Wood, Jr. Pseudonym: Spenser and West, 1969; Pages: 190 (Box 2)
    Publisher: Tiger Books/Powell Publications, Reseda
    [Spenser & West were progressive "sexologists" who wrote based off of "interviews and case histories", Introduction reads: "Oralism is the word that has been kept behind closed doors, hidden under hats and seldom spoken above a whisper. It is scorned by thousands, yet secretly enjoyed by millions and is gaining an ever-increasing circle of aficionados. Why? The hypocrisy intrigued us and we ventured forth into the land of the oralist to find out. Why is he different from other people?"]
  - A Study of Stag Films By: Edward D. Wood, Jr. Pseudonym: S. T. Lee with Dr. T. K. Peters, 1970; Pages: 192 (Box 2)
    "Sex Education Clinical Series vol. XVI"
    [contains glossary of film lingo in back, bibliography, possibly not Ed Wood, book discussions include set design, cinematography, gay films, S&M films, and art films, "‘Flaming Creatures’ is another example of underground invasion of the stag market. The film’s climactic cunnilingual rape scene is expressed with calculated crudity and very primitive photography." Also discusses Warhol amongst less pretentious pornography. "Maybe a new sexuality is upon us. Sort of a good-natured narcissism in which sex is a public demonstration whose feelings are best relished by the participant s later on...In other words, human confrontation (peace and love) has replaced human copulation. Sex as passion seems almost non-existent."] Gerhson Legman quote
  - Gay Black By: Edward D. Wood, Jr., 1970; Pages: 157 (Box 2)
    Publisher: Regency Publishing Co., El Cajon
    Reissue of Young, Black and Gay
  - Teen-Sex Swapping By: Edward D. Wood, Jr. Pseudonym: Norman Bates, 1970; Pages: c. 191 (Box 2)
    Publisher: Ben's Books Ltd., London
    [North Hollywood Barclay copyright, UK print]
  - The Adult Version of Dracula By: Edward D. Wood, Jr. Pseudonym: Anon., 1970; Pages: 190 (Box 2)
    Publisher: Calga Publishers, Inc., Los Angeles
    [part of Calga’s "Adult Versions of the World’s Standards", among these advertised were The Escapades of Cleopatra and A Jack London Trilogy. Told in an epistolary fashion via Jonathan Harker’s journal, letters, clippings, etc. From Johnathan Harker’s journal May 5th (page 33): "My flesh shivered and my hands sank lower. Across her tossing belly and down between her quivering thighs. She arched the mound of her pussy against my hand, pressing the diamond of delight into my palm."]
  - A Study of Sexual Practices in Witchcraft and Black Magic: Book 1 By: Edward D. Wood, Jr. Pseudonym: Frank Lennon with Dt. T. K. Peters, 1971; Pages: 192 (Box 2)
    "Sex Education Clinical Series vol. XVII"
    ["From time immemorial, sex and Satanism have been one and the same thing. As you will see in later pages, worship of the devil involves sexual excesses on a scale so large, that the so-called Hollywood sex orgies grow pale by comparison."] off the walls photography and captions – must reproduce
  - A Study of Sexual Practices in Witchcraft and Black Magic: Book 2 By: Edward D. Wood, Jr. Pseudonym: Frank Lennon with Dt. T. K. Peters, 1971; Pages: 192 (Box 2)
    "Sex Education Clinical Series vol. XVIII"
    ["It is not the purpose of this book to condemn, condone or to accept the Black Arts, but to set forth some facts which have been hidden deep in volumes on shelves of libraries, and hidden even deeper in court records."] off the walls photography and captions – must reproduce
  - A Study of The Sexual Man: Book Two By: Edward D. Wood, Jr. Pseudonym: Frank Leonard with Dr. T. K. Peters, 1971; Pages: 191 (Box 2)
    "Sex Education Clinical Series vol. XXXIII"
    ["Who is the sexual man? What special qualities does he possess that other men don't have? Can you become a sexual man? These are all questions that this book will answer."]
  - A Study of The Sexual Woman: Book Two By: Edward D. Wood, Jr. Pseudonym: Mandy Merrill with Dr. T. K. Peters, 1971; Pages: 191 (Box 2)
    "Sex Education Clinical Series vol. XXXI"
    "[Wood and Charles Anderson (Outlaws of the Old West), wrote and directed twelve 8mm films for SECS in 1975] possibly scan photo with captions
  - A Study of the Sons and Daughters of Erotica By: Edward D. Wood, Jr. Pseudonym: compiled by Dick Trent with Dr. T. K. Peters, 1971; Pages: 192 (Box 2)
    "Sex Education Clinical Series vol. XXVIII"
    [Akin to EDUSEX, more pornography in the guise of education, ‘...as a pictorial and editorial representation of phases and mores in our contemporary society.’ Most likely SECS was Calga Publishers since they shared the same 5585 W. Pico address. As suggested elsewhere also probably the same as Pendulum. Bibliography includes: Criswell Predicts by Criswell, Black Myth by Trent and Peters (Ed Wood) (listed as Pendulum 1971 in bibliography, listed as SECS 1971 in copy), Glen or Glenda (Wood movie), Satanic Bible by LaVey, and more.]
  - A Study of the Swappers By: Edward D. Wood, Jr. Pseudonym: S. T. Lee with Dr. T. K. Peters, 1971; Pages: 192 (Box 2)
    "Sex Education Clinical Series vol. XXVII"
  - Black Myth By: Edward D. Wood, Jr. Pseudonym: Dick Trent with Dr. T. K. Peters, 1971; Pages: 192 (Box 2)
    "Sex Education Clinical Series vol. XXII"
    ["A detailed analysis of the sexual and sociological misinformation surrounding black sexuality." It was suggested by reported ex-Pendulum/Calga writer Leo Eaton, that Dr. T. K. Peters was in fact actually a real card-carrying doctor, his website relays: "Pendulum had bought a serious, boring and excruciatingly long scientific study of sexuality from Dr. T. K. Peters. It was an unpublished manuscript that the doctor had probably labored on for years without finding a buyer (he was a Kinsey-style researcher). I hate to think what he was paid – probably peanuts – but he was very old (semi-senile was the word around the office) and he’d let it go without realizing what use would be made of it. The manuscript gave Bernie [Bloom] a sort of ‘semi-legitimacy’ for the books and magazine articles and we were all encouraged to make use of it whenever and wherever possible. Adding Dr. Peter’s name as co-writer added a spurious legitimacy." (http://www.eatoncreative.com/memories/working-with-ed-wood-jr.php)
  - The Cat's Urge By: Edward D. Wood, Jr. Pseudonym: Elliot Parker Ph.D., 1971; Pages: 160 (Box 2)
    Publisher: Echelon Book Publishers, Inc., Los Angeles
    [Contains salacious sexological case histories of female abandon - swapping, drunken sex, adulterous behavior, fetishes, and more. Page 24: "The room began to smell like a whorehouse on dollar day. Frantic, hot bodies give off a real musky smell when they’re in a close space. And that apartment was like a closet. Hell, I could have reached out and patted Benny on the butt." Page 89: "While the majority of housewives enter the forbidden world of animalism out of a profound despair, this is not an iron rule." While much of Wood’s approaches to African-American life are out and out racist, his views of Near Eastern sex practices seem to tend more towards a comical and prurient Orientalism, offensive and ignorant, but tethered to an archetypal Rohmer-esque mythological world of sexist warriors, most certainly inspired by his fascination with the exotic and supernatural. Yet, as opposed to Sax Rohmer, there is little awe and literary eloquence to counteract the reductions of the Other. Rather the notion of a misogynist Arab, painted as a savage and conquering force, is the primary abstraction of the Arab race with Wood. This point of view is apparent during a discussion of Arab sodomy on pages 136-7: "The Arab now straddled the American girl, and then his powerful maleness was at the entranceway. ‘It is the way of the East, my little love-slave.’ WIth [sic] that, he invaded. There was some sphincter tightening. Suddenly a gurgled shriek was heard as the American girl tried to push him off [...] The sex-perverted Arab was now bearing down on her as if she were some animal, some beast. She had always heard that these savage Arabs were like that, but she never knew they were so brutal. Now, a shock wave of pain tore through her narrow receptacle. Suddenly, Ahman erupted in some erotic sounding gibberish. Then, he immersed himself "to the hilt" and there was a stiffening [...] Ahman’s stiffening was rigid. Then the gushing proof of his peak flooded Valerie’s soul until she was transformed into little more than a sexual slave [...] Wordlessly, he went to the bathroom and washed himself. When he came out, bronzed and naked with his flaccid power a symbol of his superiority, he flashed a grin at her. ‘This is how we use our women in the East.’"]
  - Mary-Go-Round By: Edward D. Wood, Jr., 1972; Pages: 191 (Box 2)
    Publisher: Little Library Press, Atlanta
    [similar to Carnival Piece but more explicit as LLP tended to be.]
  - Diary of a Transvestite Hooker By: Edward D. Wood, Jr. Pseudonym: Randy, as told to Dick Trent, 1973; Pages: 182 (Box 2)
    Publisher: Eros Publishing Co., Wilmington, Del.
    [an Eros Goldstripe production, a telling of escapades in the life of transvestite hooker, told in the pictorial style. Page 173: "Summation – One might ask the question: ‘Why the life of a prostitute?’ of any number of prostitutes and there would be just as many, individually different answers...but their answers might not be considered true answers by the sociologists, sexologists and psychiatrists, because the girls themselves don’t have any true answers for themselves and why they first decided upon the profession. But the answers they give have some measure of truth, because those answers are what they believe." Page 177: "Thus it is with whores who would also like to glamorize their profession...and make a lot of money from their books in doing so... there is always a ready market for the lurid stories they reveal...imagined or otherwise...a madam, or working prostitute wrote it, therefore everything she says must be true...she lived through it. The public as well as the publisher will savor this type of material. If they were to paint their profession and what they did as some sort of dirty episode in history, then they themselves must have been dirty. Therefore...picture me pink..."]
  - Outlaws of the Old West By: Charles D. Anderson (ed.), Edward D. Wood, Jr. (contrib.), 1973; Pages: 253 (Box 2)
    Publisher: Mankind Publishing Company, Los Angeles
    Ilustrated (photo/drawing)
    The Mankind Series of Great Adventures of History
    ["Selected Readings By Mankind Magazine", contains the story "Pearl Hart and the Last Stage". Non-pornographic work in the Western genre. Tells the tale of Pearl Hart, a girl who dressed as a boy and became a famous stagecoach robber. Page 232: "She would have still been in the boys clothes she wore during the robbery, bedraggled form those days in the sale and the elements of the weather, frightened to death of the crowd which she faced." Page 234: "Although Joe Boot slipped quickly into obscurity shortly after Sheriff Truman brought the outlaw pair into Florence, the pistol and rifle-toting Pearl was just beginning to live, to be recognized, and to find her place in history. And what she didn’t conjure up in her own mind was created by the newspaper accounts of her daring adventure into the badman’s territory. Altogether, these made her break out in the cold sweats of fame." Page 235: "She had a year of ecstatic glory with the cheers of the public ringing in her ears. And then night after night the audience became thinner and thinner. The fickle public soon tires of even its most important heroes."]
  - Tales for a Sexy Night Vol. 2 By: Chuck Kelly (ed.), 1973; Pages: 160 (Box 2)
    Publisher: Gallery Press, Los Angeles
    Illustrated by Neil Weisbecker
    [contains stories by Edw. D. Wood, Jr., "Final Curtain", "To Kill a Saturday Night" (this one is a Beckett-esque masterpiece, should be excerpted), "Craps", and "Calamity Jane Loves Hosenose Kate Loves Cattle Anne". Also includes a contribution from collaborator Charles D. Anderson.]
  - TV Lust By: Edward D. Wood, Jr. Pseudonym: Dick Trent, 1977; Pages: 180 (Box 2)
    Transexual Library
    [Written a year before his death, Hayes describes "The rigors of writing smut were definitely telling on Wood at this point. The rehashed plot of the transvestite hitman certainly wasn’t original this time around, and the usual colorful characters are almost nonexistent. The flair that made some of his other novels and films bearable, even through a thin plot and the strange grammar, was noticeably absent from TV Lust. It seems as though Ed Wood had finally given up." Page 40: "Chris slipped into the fur-like coat, and he was ready for his first walk on the street in girl’s clothes... he was elated nearly to the point of exploding...Chris mixed another pitcher of martinis and this time had poured a double before he went back to the big chair. The pistol lay on the floor near the attaché case. He liked the idea of the fur coat on the bed, it was going to be just as cold that night as it had been that October so long ago."]
  - Let Me Die in Drag By: Edward D. Wood, Jr., 1995; Pages: 172 (Box 2)
    Publisher: Gorse, London
    [modern reprint of Pad Library’s Let Me Die in Drag]
- Series II. Magazines and Other Published Material
  - "Glen or Glenda?", movie poster, 1953 (Map-case Z-17)
  - "The Undergraduate", movie poster, 1971 (Map-case Z-17)
  - Fetish in Films No. 1, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    Includes an image taken from "For Love and Money"
  - Caper Vol. 13 No. 8, Feb. 1969 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    Includes the article "Guilding The Ghouls" discussing the "ghoulie flick"
  - Case Histories Vol. 2 No. 2, Aug./Sept. 1971 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    Includes "A Nation of Peepers" by Norman Bates (pseudonym)
    Includes "The Day the Mummy Returned" by Edward D. Wood, Jr.
  - Pendulum Vol. 3 No. 3, Aug./Sept. 1971 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    Includes "Into My Grave" by Edward D. Wood, Jr.
  - Lezo Vol. 5 No. 3, Aug./Sept. 1971 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    Includes "The Night the Banshee Cried" by Edward D. Wood, Jr.
  - Belly Button Vol. 2 No. 3, Nov./Dec. 1971 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    Includes "The Wave Off" by Edward D. Wood, Jr.
    Includes "Sex and the Future" by Norman Bates (pseudonym)q
  - Horror Sex Tales Vol. 1 No. 1, Jan. 1972 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    Includes "Hellfire" by Edward D. Wood, Jr.
    Includes "Scream Your Bloody Head Off" by Edward D. Wood, Jr.
    Includes "The Rue Morgue Re-visited: by Dick Trent (pseudonym)
    Includes "Witches of Amau Ra" by Dick Trent (pseudonym)
    Includes "Bums Rush Terror" by Ann Gora (pseudonym)
  - Suck-Em-Up Vol. 2 No. 1, Mar./Apr. 1972 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    Includes " 'You Gotta' Have A Fetish' 'You Gotta' Have A Gimmick' " by Ann Gora (pseudonym)
  - Savage Sex Vol. 4 No. 2, Apr./May 1972 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    Includes "The Responsibility Game" by Dick Trent (pseudonym)
  - Body and Soul Vol. 6 No. 2, July/Aug. 1972 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    Includes "Scene of the Crime" by Edward D. Wood, Jr.
    Includes "What Would We Have Done Without Them?" by Edward D. Wood, Jr.
  - Weird Sex Tales Vol. 1 No. 1, July/Aug. 1972 (Box 3, Folder 11)
    Includes "Ant Hell" by Alvin Tostig (pseudonym)
    Includes "News Read-Out" edited by Norman Bates (pseudonym)
  - Monster Sex Tales Vol. 1 No. 1, Aug./Sept. 1972 (Box 3, Folder 12)
    Includes "Castle of Dracula" by Chester Winfield (probable pseudonym)
    Includes "The Voyage of Dracula" by Roy Hemp (probable pseudonym)
    Includes "Lust of the Vampire" by Dudley McDonly (probable pseudonym)
  - Legendary Sex Tales Vol. 1 No. 1, Sept./Oct. 1972 (Box 3, Folder 13)
    Includes "Cleopatra's Sex Slave" by Dudley McDonly (probable pseudonym)
  - Orgy Vol. 4 No. 2, Sept./Oct. 1972 (Box 3, Folder 14)
    Includes "The Core of Vampire" by Ann Gora (pseudonym)
    Includes "Slap It To 'Em" by Dick Trent (pseudonym)
  - Orgy Vol. 5 No. 1, Jan./Feb. 1973 (Box 3, Folder 15)
    Includes "A Taste of Blood" by Edward D. Wood, Jr.
    Includes "Seek and Ye Shall Find" by Dick Trent (pseudonym)
  - Hellcats Vol. 2 No. 1, Jan./Feb. 1973 (Box 3, Folder 16)
    Includes "Trade Secrets" by Shirlee Lane (pseudonym)
    Includes "Lesbian Understanding" by Ann Gora (pseudonym)
  - Swap Vol. 7 No. 1, Jan./Feb. 1973 (Box 3, Folder 17)
    Includes "The Divorcee's Problem" by Ann Gora (pseudonym)
  - Turn On Vol. 2 No. 3, June/July 1973 (Box 3, Folder 18)
    Includes "The Creeping Sexation" edited by Edward D. Wood, Jr.
    Includes "Why a Prostitute's Life" by Dick Trent (pseudonym)
  - Body and Soul Vol. 8 No. 1, May/June 1975 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Body and Soul Annual, 1975? (Box 3, Folder 20)
    Includes "The Home Scene" by Edward D. Wood, Jr.
    Includes "The Sport of Bored Lovers" by Norman Bates (pseudonym)
  - Ace Vol. 21 No. 6, Dec. 1976 (Box 3, Folder 21)
    Includes "Sheep in Wolf's Clothing" by Edward Wood
    Includes "How Erotica Turns Her On" by William P. Evans (pseudonym)
  - Femme Fatales Vol. 7 No. 1, June 1998 (Box 3, Folder 22)
    Includes "Orgy of the Dead Ed Wood's Post- "Plan 9" Legacy: Bonding Spirits and Strippers-in Color!" by Laura Schiff
  - Outre No. 16, 1999 (Box 3, Folder 23)
    Includes "From Ed Wood to Elvis! The Incredible Saga of Dolores Fuller" by Greg Douglas
    Includes "Hollywood Rat Race! How to Make a Cheap Picture and Fail" by Ed Wood, Jr.
- Series III. Exhibition Material
  - Print Outs
    - Ace Magazine (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - A Study of Censorship, Sex, and the Movies bk.2 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - A Study of Sexual Practices and Witchcraft v.1 and v.2 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - A Study of Stag Films (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Bellybutton Magazine (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Body and Soul Magazine (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Bye Bye Broadie (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Glen or Glenda (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Horror Sex Tales Magazine (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - Monster Sex Tales Magazine (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - Orgy of the Dead (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - Sleeze Paperbacks (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - Tales for a Sexy Night (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - The Book of the Sexual Woman, The Book of the Sexual Man (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - The Erotic Spy (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - The Sons and Daughters of Erotica (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - Various Magazine Printouts (Box 4, Folder 17)
    - Various Novel Printouts (Box 4, Folder 18)
    - Weird Sex Tales Magazine (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Drafts
    - Catalogue Drafts (Box 4, Folder 20)
    - Research Writing Drafts (Box 4, Folder 21)
    - Text Drafts (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Exhibit Placards (Box 4)
- Series IV. Films
  - "The Incredibly Strange Film Show, volume 3: Ed Wood", Date unknown; DVD-2348
SEPARATED MATERIAL
The following materials have been separated from the collection. Some have been cataloged individually:
A Study of Fetishes & Fantasies
By: Edward D. Wood, Jr.
Pseudonym: Norman Bates & Dick Trent
Location: Human Sexuality HQ57.3 .W77 1973
Pages: 191 Published: 1971
[indicative of the fast and loose publishing culture: though the outer boards attribute the book to Wood & Bates, inside title page attributes "by Norman Bates & Dick Trent". Bibliography of this "educational" book cites a myriad of sources including Freud, Krafft-Ebing, Stekel, and Theodore Sturgeon.]
A Study in the Motivation of Censorship, Sex & The Movies: Book I
By: Edward D. Wood, Jr.
Location: Human Sexuality PN1995.9.S45 S89 1973 bk.1
Pages: 190 Published: 1973
[the EDUSEX Press imprint under Gallery was similar to SECS in that in provided an educational guise for pornography that made it exempt from obscenity prosecution, this "study" in particular allowed Wood to flex his knowledge of the film world. Preface reads: "The President’s Commission on Obscenity and Pornography has found that the law ‘is not the only or necessarily the most effective way’ to deal with pornography. The report recommends a massive and extensive sex education program to blunt the American’s taste for smut and to forge an informed public consensus on the problem."]
A Study in the Motivation of Censorship, Sex & The Movies: Book II
By: Edward D. Wood, Jr.